<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title></title>
        <link>undefined</link>
        <description>undefined</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 18:34:43 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>Joplin Pages Publisher</generator>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Setup Linkedin Webhooks]]></title>
            <guid>184bbf4e8f0b4008a30dbe0eb5901678</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 17:49:03 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>To get alerts via LinkedIn's API webhooks whenever your company makes a post, you will need to follow these general steps:</p>
<ol>
<li>Register your app on the LinkedIn Developer Platform:</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Go to the LinkedIn Developer Platform website and sign in with your LinkedIn account.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Create a new app and provide the necessary information such as the app name, description, and website URL.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Select the appropriate API products for your app, in this case, the Marketing Developer Platform.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Set up your app's authentication and authorization by creating a LinkedIn app access token.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<ol start="3">
<li>Subscribe to company page updates:</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Use the LinkedIn Marketing Developer Platform API to subscribe to updates for your company page.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>You will need to provide your LinkedIn app access token and the appropriate API endpoints for subscribing to updates.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<ol start="5">
<li>Set up webhooks to receive alerts:</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Use the LinkedIn Marketing Developer Platform API to set up webhooks for receiving alerts.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>You will need to provide the appropriate API endpoints for receiving the webhook notifications.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Make sure that your webhook endpoint is secure and can handle the expected traffic.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<ol start="7">
<li>Test your app and webhook:</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Create a test post on your company page to ensure that your app is receiving the webhook notifications.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Make sure that the webhook payload includes the information you need, such as the post text and image.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<ol start="9">
<li>Handle errors and manage alerts:</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Handle any errors that may occur, such as failed webhook deliveries or invalid payloads.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Manage the alerts you receive by storing them in a database or sending them to a notification service.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Please note that the exact steps may vary depending on your specific use case and the programming language and frameworks you are using. You may also need to refer to LinkedIn's developer documentation for more detailed information on using their API and webhooks.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>