<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title></title>
        <link>undefined</link>
        <description>undefined</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 16:20:59 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>Joplin Pages Publisher</generator>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[09/03/2023 - Amnesia Seedlings starting to sprout]]></title>
            <guid>d665318121f843f283092316de4ba730</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 03:35:09 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>ChatGPT is saying that they should be ready for harvest between <strong>November 10, 2023, and December 1, 2023</strong>. We put them in water on August 25th.</p>
<p>Excited to see how they look! Going to start a grow journal for this plant and hopefully do a better job of tracking it.</p>
<p>We still need to order more rocket fuel.</p>
<p>We need to figure out a better automated water situation? Specifically the lid of the existing bag keeps coming off which could contaminate the water. I should 3d print something that allows air to go through but not bugs and dust.</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/4a1a5cfab20e47ca9a4a85edc9439dc6.jpg" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Growing Products]]></title>
            <guid>eddc7557e7db470d86469e1ae2f9e266</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 00:30:24 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I didn't have a green thumb before this, but it was a cool learning experience. I started by growing with no nutrients and walmart soil, and the results were pretty sad. I slowly upgraded from there. I watched a ton of youtube videos and after 3 grows, I'd say I finally feel like I kinda sorta know the beginning's of what I'm doing lol. Tara likes training the plants to grow sideways so you get multiple mega buds at the top instead of just 1. We got like 6 off one plant this time, it was awesome! And kinda therapuetic, like doing a bonzai. If you haven't grown before, these are the things I can't live without now.</p>
<table>
<thead>
<tr>
<th></th>
<th></th>
<th></th>
<th></th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td>Name</td>
<td>Description</td>
<td>Cost</td>
<td>Link</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Automated Pump</td>
<td>Decent pump I leave plugged in. I run it for 3 minutes everyday and that works pretty well</td>
<td>$29.99</td>
<td><a title="https://amzn.to/44y0Isx" href="https://amzn.to/44y0Isx">Amazon Link</a></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Water Bag</td>
<td>Using this bag with the pump, I go about a week without having to water the plants:</td>
<td>$15.24</td>
<td><a title="https://amzn.to/3L6aKKC" href="https://amzn.to/3L6aKKC">Amazon Link</a></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Rogue Fuel</td>
<td>This soil has all the nutrients you need so you don't absolutely need nutrients, but if you use the nutrients, they help make the buds ridiculously big.</td>
<td>$45.68</td>
<td><a title="https://amzn.to/47XQHaW" href="https://amzn.to/47XQHaW">Amazon Link</a></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Grow Big by Fox Farms</td>
<td>These are the nutrients I am using. I did a grow without them and one with and the difference was astounding. After the leaves come out I used grow big in the middle for pretty much all of it.</td>
<td>$41.99</td>
<td><a title="https://amzn.to/3Z02tO2" href="https://amzn.to/3Z02tO2">Amazon Link</a></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Cal Mag</td>
<td>If you use shitty soil like I did at first, you may get big white spots on your leaves, this fixes it:</td>
<td>$20.19</td>
<td><a title="https://a.co/d/2HZfeGW" href="https://a.co/d/2HZfeGW">Amazon Link</a></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Grow Tent</td>
<td>I used this tent, I can fit like 4-5 big 7 gallon plants in this one:</td>
<td>$108.12</td>
<td><a title="https://amzn.to/3sugSFZ" href="https://amzn.to/3sugSFZ">Amazon Link</a></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Grow Light</td>
<td>This is the light I use, it is really strong, and you can kinda see it peaking out the seams of the tent. I can't close the tent because it gets too hot out here.</td>
<td>$139.99</td>
<td><a title="https://amzn.to/3P0RKym" href="https://amzn.to/3P0RKym">Amazon Link</a></td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p>Total Cost: $401.20</p>
<p>I have a bunch of other stuff now, like thermometer, and shit, but I think everything else is extra, this is like the minimum I need to grow. Next I'm going to put a greenhouse on our land with AC to do a much bigger grow, but not just of cannabis, but food too. My ADHD super power is automation (or being lazy as shit lol) so I want to apply that to the greenhouse so we can still travel.</p>
<p>I use the image below to get my language correct:</p>
<p><img src="/_resources/12f634c484444e088fc4f0f8fc068abe.png" /></p>
<p> </p>
]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Setup Linkedin Webhooks]]></title>
            <guid>184bbf4e8f0b4008a30dbe0eb5901678</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 17:49:03 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>To get alerts via LinkedIn's API webhooks whenever your company makes a post, you will need to follow these general steps:</p>
<ol>
<li>Register your app on the LinkedIn Developer Platform:</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Go to the LinkedIn Developer Platform website and sign in with your LinkedIn account.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Create a new app and provide the necessary information such as the app name, description, and website URL.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Select the appropriate API products for your app, in this case, the Marketing Developer Platform.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Set up your app's authentication and authorization by creating a LinkedIn app access token.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<ol start="3">
<li>Subscribe to company page updates:</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Use the LinkedIn Marketing Developer Platform API to subscribe to updates for your company page.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>You will need to provide your LinkedIn app access token and the appropriate API endpoints for subscribing to updates.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<ol start="5">
<li>Set up webhooks to receive alerts:</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Use the LinkedIn Marketing Developer Platform API to set up webhooks for receiving alerts.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>You will need to provide the appropriate API endpoints for receiving the webhook notifications.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Make sure that your webhook endpoint is secure and can handle the expected traffic.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<ol start="7">
<li>Test your app and webhook:</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Create a test post on your company page to ensure that your app is receiving the webhook notifications.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Make sure that the webhook payload includes the information you need, such as the post text and image.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<ol start="9">
<li>Handle errors and manage alerts:</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Handle any errors that may occur, such as failed webhook deliveries or invalid payloads.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Manage the alerts you receive by storing them in a database or sending them to a notification service.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Please note that the exact steps may vary depending on your specific use case and the programming language and frameworks you are using. You may also need to refer to LinkedIn's developer documentation for more detailed information on using their API and webhooks.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beyond the Skies: Exploring the World Through a Flight Attendant’s Lens]]></title>
            <guid>b31ef3cd07894c13ac3d3bb3488541ed</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 07:55:20 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As a flight attendant, you would think that travel to exotic destinations and international locales would be a given. Sadly, as our latest trip has shown, not all flight attendants travel for fun. My wife runs a small tour agency that caters to flight attendants called Crew Travelers, and we are currently in the middle of our trip to Lesvos, Greece. So far it has been an amazing experience getting to know all the flight attendants. I feel like flight attendants are consistently the coolest people you can meet.</p>
<p>Each one is different and unique but our job unites us in a way that makes us all feel like family. Our struggles and lifestyles are similar, creating a camaraderie that anyone in the workplace knows.</p>
<p>I find it interesting how most of our travelers are first time international travelers. As flight attendants, our jobs can be so hectic that traveling for fun can seem pretty daunting. When you are told where to fly, and where to stay, it can build a feeling of complacency when you travel. Instead of harboring independence, our job can breed familiarity and complacency.</p>
<p>When we fly as flight attendants, every aspect of our trip is taken care of. Our flight attendant app tells us where we need to be, who will pick us up, and even gives us access to our contract, which gives us a sense of protection when we are working that there limits how much abuse we have to deal with.</p>
<p>Compare that to flying on your own where you are in complete control of your destiny. Want a hotel? You gotta book it. Need a flight? Up to you to book it. Transportation to and from the hotel? That's on you if your hotel doesn't cover it. Stuck at the airport because flights are full? Sorry, no contract will get you out of that.</p>
<p>With all that being said, travel is good for you. It gives you confidence in yourself. It forces you to solve problems that you would normally not face and gets you out of your comfort zone. It gives you stories and experiences that no one can take away from you. It makes you a more varied and interesting human being. When you are with your friends, it gives you something to say.</p>
<p>The list of places that my wife and I have been to is long and varied. Every other month or so we get an itch to see someplace new. A new country, a new experience, a new culture. It's addictive, especially when your flights cost about as much as a bus ride. Our hope is to someday find the perfect place to retire. Until then, we revel in our wanderlust and we can't wait to see what new adventures we stumble upon!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[My Path To Flight Attendant]]></title>
            <guid>f40ecfcff34a42478312851f56d7c3b3</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2013 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1 id="my-path-to-flight-attendant">My Path To Flight Attendant</h1>
<p><strong>Tags</strong>: No categories found</p>
<p><strong>Date</strong>: Thu, 01 Aug 2013 22:05:35 +0000</p>
<p>Wow, what an adventure! So yesterday, I finished the final part of the hiring process with a major airlines to become a flight attendant. It was not an easy process or a quick one, and I hope this blog post helps answer any questions that you might have about the whole process. I became interested in this position thanks to my uncle, who has been a flight attendant for over 27 years with US Airways, and who absolutely loves it! Keep reading for the process I went through to be hired!</p>
<p><img src="https://djangelic.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/08/the_giant_approaches.jpg" alt="test" /></p>
<p>The Video Interview</p>
<p>It all starts with a video interview. This was actually not what I expected. I thought that maybe I would be connecting through Skype or some other program to a live representative and we would be initiating a normal interview that way. It is actually a video recording of you, talking to your webcam (or if<br />
you don't have a webcam, they have a call in option that allows you to record your voice), and asking you questions. These questions are very basic, and two of them that stood out to me where "Why do you want to become a flight attendant" and "Why do you think you would make a good flight attendant." This was easily the scariest part for me, since I was not able to see the person, and you only really get one try per question. I had a lot of Umm's and Ahhh's in there, and was sure I did not pass at all. Thankfully I did, and I attribute a lot of it to SMILING!! I am a happy person in general, and this<br />
helped a lot! I smiled throughout the whole thing. A few days after the video interview, I got an email stating that I had passed the video interview, and I<br />
was ready to move on the next part of the interview, the in person group interview.</p>
<p><img src="https://djangelic.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/08/observatory_tower_lincoln_castle.jpg" alt="One of the main reasons I want to fly, is to visit castles such as this one" /></p>
<p>One of the main reasons I want to fly, is to visit castles such as this one</p>
<h3 id="in-person-group-interview">In Person Group Interview</h3>
<p>This was easily the most fun out of the whole process! They flew me out to Dallas TX to interview with around 30 other applicants. I was given the option to fly out the night before and pay for my own hotel, or fly out the day of. I went the day before, so I would be rested for the interview. When I arrived at<br />
the training area, it was amazing! It is like a giant resort, mostly for their trainees and a few other companies. The trainees live there for two and a half<br />
months during training, and it becomes a home away from home. After checking in the front desk, because I was an hour early, I sat down and noticed a few other people waiting, and started up a conversation with them. They were also applicants, and they were just as excited and nervous as I was. After we entered, the process was pretty straightforward. They had different team building exercises and activities to get to know us a bit better and to see how we interacted with each other. My advice to you here is this. SMILE! Smile<br />
smile smile! Be happy you are there, and excited! Greet everyone you meet! Try to be a leader in the activities if you can, and show the interviewers that<br />
you are confident. At the end of the day, we had our two interviews, a four person panel interview, and a one on one interview. Just remember to be yourself, and again, smile! If you did well, you will be taken separately and fingerprinted in anticipation of the next step, the background check!</p>
<h3><img src="https://djangelic.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/08/james_i_think_your_covers_blown.jpg" alt="Background Check" /></h3>
<p>The Background Check</p>
<p>This part is pretty straight forward. If you passed the group interview, you<br />
will be asked to provide a history of your work background, and more<br />
information. This will take a few days, and if you pass, you will need to go<br />
back to dallas for the next step in the process, The Drug Exam and Agility<br />
Exam.</p>
<h3 id="-2"><img src="https://djangelic.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/08/gettinghugejpg.jpg" alt="getting-huge.jpg" /></h3>
<p>The Drug Exam and Agility Exam</p>
<p>This part should be quite straightforward, you will be required to do a drug<br />
exam, and agility test, although in my case, I was flown out to Dallas to do<br />
this as well. I think the drug exam part is pretty straightforward of course<br />
(make sure to disclose any medication you are taking, and be prepared to have<br />
your doctor send a letter regarding any strong medications you take on a<br />
regular basis), but the agility exam could be difficult if you are a smaller<br />
woman. You will be required to push a certain amount of weight (they don't<br />
tell you exactly how much, but the general consensus is 60 pounds to push,<br />
pull, and lift, all the while maintaining a specific heart rate. Thats pretty<br />
much the final step. If you pass here, you will be invited to the next part,<br />
the Training Process.</p>
<h3 id="the-training-process">The Training Process</h3>
<p>If you have continued to read this, congrats! But here is the tough part. If<br />
you make it through all of this, then you will be invited to go to the Flight<br />
Attendant training. Please keep in mind, you it is two and half months of<br />
unpaid training (room, board, and food will be provided), and from everything<br />
I have read, it is not easy training. Make sure you have enough money in the<br />
bank to cover your bills during that time. I am super excited to start my new<br />
adventure as a flight attendant, and I am looking forward to it! The perks are<br />
awesome, and being able to see the world is an opportunity I don't want to<br />
miss out on. Hope to see you in the air!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Turing Test and the Essence of Humanity]]></title>
            <guid>5bf7b688f1b74ecb890dd4128f023d71</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2010 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Recently, I found myself engrossed in a captivating read about artificial intelligence (AI) and the Turing test. This exploration led me down a rabbit hole of introspection about what truly defines us as humans and how our decisions, both big and small, shape the tapestry of our lives.</p>
<p><strong>The Turing Test Explained</strong></p>
<p>For those unfamiliar, the Turing test was conceived by Alan Turing, a pioneer in the world of computer science. The test's premise is simple yet profound: place a human and a computer in separate rooms, and have another human interact with both through text. If the person cannot reliably distinguish between the computer and the human based solely on their responses, the computer is said to have passed the Turing test. In essence, it's a measure of a machine's ability to exhibit intelligent behavior indistinguishable from that of a human.</p>
<p><strong>The Intricacies of Human Decision-Making</strong></p>
<p>What struck me most about this concept is the vast complexity of human decision-making. Our choices are often a web of interconnected events, influenced by a myriad of factors. While machines make decisions based on logic and data, humans often incorporate emotions, past experiences, and even societal pressures into their choices.</p>
<p>Take smoking as an example. From a purely logical standpoint, given the well-documented health risks, one would assume the decision to avoid smoking is straightforward. Yet, millions continue to smoke. Why? Because human decisions often factor in intangibles like peer pressure, societal perceptions, and emotional states. A computer, when presented with the same data, would likely conclude that smoking is detrimental and should be avoided. But humans, with our intricate web of emotions and experiences, might arrive at a different conclusion.</p>
<p><strong>Emotion: The Quintessential Human Trait</strong></p>
<p>This brings me to a pivotal realization: the essence of humanity might very well lie in our capacity for emotion. Robots, no matter how advanced, don't feel joy, sorrow, love, or fear. They don't make choices based on a gut feeling, a past heartbreak, or a fleeting whim. Humans, on the other hand, are often guided by these very emotions, even when they defy logic.</p>
<p>Our brains, unlike computers, aren't just organic processors. They're repositories of memories, emotions, and abstract thoughts. We associate decisions with past experiences, future aspirations, and a plethora of emotions. This depth of feeling, which can't be quantified or programmed, is perhaps what truly separates us from machines.</p>
<p><strong>In Conclusion</strong></p>
<p>While AI and machines continue to advance, achieving feats once thought impossible, there remains an intangible essence to humanity that can't be replicated. It's our ability to feel, to empathize, and to make decisions that can't always be explained by logic. In my humble opinion, it's this rich tapestry of emotions and experiences that makes us uniquely human.</p>
<p><em>Author: Angel M via ChatGPT4 Rewrite for readability from this entry: d2b22bc56f204be7aa486a398d1091ee.</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>